Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/amiel-fababeir-849771248 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Decision-Making
Project Management
Technical Support

Certifications

The Employee's Guide to Sustainability

Windows Server 2012 Installation and Configuration

Problem Analysis and Decision Making

COA (CYBER SECURITY 101)

Administration Backup and Recovery

Amiel Fababeir

09651290346

Rizal, Calabarzon, Philippines

Summary

My name is Amiel Fababeir, and I hold a Bachelor of Science in Information Systems. I have six years of experience in the IT field, specializing in technical support and NOC administration. My skills include hardware troubleshooting, SQL data filtering, and basic network troubleshooting. I'm dedicated to providing efficient solutions and enhancing system performance.

Experience

Electronic Commerce Payments (ECPay) Inc. NOC admin December 2019 - Present (5 years 1 month)

SmartPetro
Field Technician
November 2017 - September 2019 (1 year 11 months)
Makati, National Capital Region, Philippines

Education

ACLC College

Bachelor's degree Information System, Information Technology \cdot (June 2014 - May 2017)